module.exports = [
    {
        question: "How many sisters does Joey have?",
        option1: "5",
        option2: "6",
        option3: "7",
        option4: "8",
        answer: "7"
    },
    {
        question: "In The One Where Monica Gets a Roommate, what did Ross say JUST before Rachel walked through the door in a wedding dress?",
        option1: "I just want to a million dollar",
        option2: "I just want to be married again",
        option3: "I just want a wife",
        option4: "I just want to have a wife again",
        answer: "I just want to a million dollar"
    },
    {
        question: "In The One with the Sonogram at the End, where did Rachel lose her engagement ring?",
        option1: "In the bathroom",
        option2: "In the fruit bowl",
        option3: "Under the sofa cushions",
        option4: "In the lasagna",
        answer: "In the lasagna"
    },
    {
        question: "In The One with the Thumb, what kind of phone did Phoebe’s bank send her as an apology for putting too much money into her account?",
        option1: "A high heel phone",
        option2: "A football phone",
        option3: "A dog phone",
        option4: "A pair of lips phone",
        answer: "A football phone"
    },
    {
        question: "In The One with George Stephanopoulo s, what kind of pizza did the girls originally order for their sleepover?",
        option1: "An extra large pepperoni",
        option2: "A deep dish Chicago style",
        option3: "A mushroom, green pepper, and onion",
        option4: "A fat free crust with extra cheese",
        answer: "A fat free crust with extra cheese"
    },
    {
        question: "Where did Carol first meet Susan?",
        option1: "At college",
        option2: "At work",
        option3: "At the gym",
        option4: "At central perk",
        answer: "At the gym"
    },
    {
        question: "How did Susan and Ross come up with Ben’s name?",
        option1: "It was the doctor's name",
        option2: "They both had uncles named Ben",
        option3: "It's the name of their favorite actor",
        option4: "It was on the janitor's name tag",
        answer: "It was on the janitor's name tag"
    },
    {
        question: "What were Ben's first words?",
        option1: "Hi",
        option2: "Bye",
        option3: "Mom",
        option4: "Dumb",
        answer: "Hi"
    },
    {
        question: "How long did Ross and Emily date before they got engaged?",
        option1: "14 days",
        option2: "6 weeks",
        option3: "A year",
        option4: "3 months",
        answer: "6 weeks"
    },
    {
        question: "Rachel left Ross a drunken voicemail confessing her feelings after Ross and Julie were about to take what big relationship step?",
        option1: "Move in together",
        option2: "Get a cat together",
        option3: "Elope",
        option4: "Meet Julie's parents",
        answer: "Get a cat together"
    }
]